Viewers, you will not expect me to say, "Breakthrough".
Even if there is a breakthrough, without the Word of God in your heart,
will you be able to maintain breakthrough?
Don't let us deceive ourselves. Vanity upon vanity.
Even if there is a breakthrough for you and there is no Word of God in your heart,
how will you maintain it?
It's better not to have breakthrough than to have it and lose it.
Indeed, I hear breakthrough but I don't know how you will maintain it
because without the Word of God in your heart, it will be difficult to maintain.
What you have received in the past is what you are here for again today.
Your business was going well but suddenly went down.
You cannot maintain this blessing without the Word of God in your heart.
Look at your marriage: The thing was smooth but later...
You cannot maintain them without the Word of God in your heart.
Look at what is going on: things go...
You will not be able to maintain your life without the Word of God in your heart.
Tell your neighbour, "My heart, hear the voice of God".
If I were you, this is what I would continue to meditate on.
Your heart is the real man.
You - just your appearance is a camouflage.
Tell your neighbour, "Your appearance is a camouflage.
The real person is your heart".
Tell your neighbour; face your neighbour.
Say, "My appearance is a camouflage".
Maybe you may not understand the camouflage I am talking about.
You know soldiers? When they are going to war, they put on the uniform.
That uniform is a camouflage.
What is working in them is their heart;
how they control strategy and tactic, holding gun and ammunition.
But the uniform they put on is just... - anybody can wear uniform.
Say to your neighbour, "My appearance is a camouflage.
My heart is the main man".
Viewers, the Word in our heart is our contact with God.
I say to your heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Awake, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The Holy Spirit is at the door of your heart,
knocking the door of your heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You must have a free heart.
By this free heart, your heart can contact the Holy Spirit,
have access to the Holy Spirit.
Awake, in the name of Jesus!
I say to my heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Yes.
Like I have said:
Committing the Word of God to memory is valuable but does not bring Jesus to the scene.
Awake, in the name of Jesus!
I say to your heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Learning the Hebrew, whatever language in the Bible, the history of the Books of the Bible
is valuable but does not bring Jesus to the scene.
I say to your heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Awake, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
To celebrate a new year is to celebrate it with all your heart.
Any celebration, if your heart does not act with the Word of God, nothing can be achieved.
In the name of God, nothing can be achieved.
In the name of Jesus, nothing can be achieved.
No one can say, "Jesus is the Lord" without the Word of God in the heart.
I say to your heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever our heart engages on influences our conduct and our character.
Your heart, hear the voice of God, in the name of Jesus!
Hear the voice of God, in the name of Jesus!
The same heart, the Holy Spirit expresses Himself through.
He wants to talk to you through your heart.
Heart means your spirit.
I say to your heart, "Awake, in the name of Jesus!"
Awake, in the name of Jesus!
Now, how do we awake this heart?
The Bible says you become an integral part of the Word of God by meditation.
Awake, in the name of Jesus!
Become an integral part, in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord, in Jesus' name.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 13/01/2019